hello and welcome back to new every day
こんにちは、 毎日 新しいものへようこそ。
my name is Carrie and my name is Jen and
私の名前はCarrieで、私の名前はJenと
on today's show we feel a song coming on
今日のショーでは、私たちは歌が来るのを感じる
we're going to take a look at some of
私たちはいくつかの
the key Psalms that you've probably
おそらくあなたがしている重要な詩篇
heard a hundred times but I'm delve and
百回聞いたが、私は掘り下げている
a little bit deeper and say do they have
少し深く、彼らは持っていると言う
to say to us tune in activation
私たちに言えば
you've got mad skills now hone them
あなたは今、それらを磨く狂ったスキルを持っている
learn new skills or improve your
新しいスキルを習得したり、
existing ones with online video
既存のものとオンラインビデオ
tutorials and training from Linda calm
Linda calmからのチュートリアルとトレーニング
through our special link at cat five dot
cat 5 dotで私たちの特別リンクを介して
TV / Linda learn software technology
TV / Lindaはソフトウェア技術を学ぶ
creative and business skills you can use
あなたが使用できる創造的なビジネススキル
today to help you achieve your
今日はあなたの
professional goals join today and start
プロフェッショナルな目標が今日に加わりスタート
learning will give you this chance to
学習はあなたにこのチャンスを与えます
try it absolutely free with unlimited
無制限で自由に試してみてください
access to all of the courses sign up now
すべて のコースへのアクセスは今すぐ申し込む
for free cat5 dot TV / linda
無料cat5ドットテレビ/リンダのために
welcome back to you every day so by that
そんなことで毎日あなたに歓迎します。
you tuned in Jen we've already passed
私たちはすでに合格したJenで調整した
Christmas we've passed new years and
私たちは新しい年を過ごしました。
passed paying off of our bills and we're
私たちの請求書を払い戻し、私たちは
ready for whatever is next that's right
次のものがあればすぐに準備ができている
so so glad that you've tuned in wherever
あなたがどこにいても調整してくれてとても嬉しいです
you're at wherever you are in the world
あなたはどこにいてもあなたは世界にいます
we're always amazed with all the viewers
私たちは常にすべての視聴者に驚いています
that we see from Brazil we saw someone
私たちはブラジルから見ると誰かが見えた
in Brazil France where else was there
ブラジルではどこにいたのですか？
Jen all over the USA it's all over the
Jenはアメリカ全土で
US so thank you so much thank you to the
米国はとてもありがとう
people who are generously supporting us
寛大に私たちを支えている人々
through your gifts if you go to our
あなたが 私たちに 行くならあなたの贈り物を通して
website new everyday TV and click our
ウェブサイトの新しい毎日のテレビをクリックしてください
partners page you can go to patreon and
パートナーのページでは、patreonと
from there you can donate a quarter each
そこからあなたはそれぞれ4分の1を寄付することができます
episode 25 cents or maybe a dollar each
エピソード25セントまたはおそらく1ドル
episode and that's really going to help
エピソードとそれは本当に助けになる
us out and help Robbie Ferguson and the
私たちアウトとロビー・ファーガソンを助け、
team from category 5 TV keep new
カテゴリ5テレビのチームが新しい状態を維持
everyday strong so thanks so much mm-hmm
毎日強いのでとてもありがとうmm-hmm
so Jen on today's show we are going to
そうジェンは、今日の番組で、我々はしようとしています
look at some one Psalm in particular but
特に詩篇を見てください。
the Book of Psalms is actually like a
詩篇の書は実際には
songbook o is the song book in the Old
songbook o は Oldの曲の本です
Testament and it's comprised by a lot of
聖書とそれは多く の
people King David wrote a majority of
人々はダビデ王の大多数を書いた
the Psalms King Solomon the sons of
ソロモンの詩篇
Korah Moses which is very interesting
非常に興味深いコサ・モーセ
wrote one of the Psalms and i do not
詩篇の一つを書きました。 私は
know that I know that's cool eh you're
私が知っていることを知っているそれはあなたがすごいですねえ
not something on your big day every day
あなたの大切な日に毎日何かではない
I know new everyday look we can just
私は毎日のような新しい日常を知っている
turn to Psalm 90 and and it says a
詩篇90に目を向けると、
prayer of Moses the man of God so this
このように神の人であるモーセの祈り
is the psalm I believe that is he wrote
私はそれがある賛美歌と信じ ている 彼が書きました
coming up out of the Red Sea okay yes so
紅海から出てくるよ
as I flip back so it's very interesting
私は戻ってくるので、とても面白いです。
we often think that all of the songs
私たちはしばしば、すべての 曲
that are in the Old Testaments are only
旧約聖書に書かれているのは
in the book of Song
歌の本に
but there's a song of Miriam right and
Miriamの曲があります
this is the song of Moses and then song
これはモーセの歌であり、その後の歌です
of David and in Samuel yes and then
ダビデとサミュエルとの間にはい、そして
Deborah has a psalm a song in the book
デボラはその本の中で賛美歌を持っています
of Judges really yes so it is very
裁判官のは本当にそうので、それは非常にあります
interesting as you read through the Old
あなたが古くから読んだように面白い
Testament that you find these different
あなたがこれらの異なる
Psalms and so I'm going to trust that
詩篇などを信じるつもりです
Robbie is going to do his magic because
ロビーは彼の魔法をやるつもりだから
I'm i cannot currently find where it is
私は現在どこにいるのかは分からない
that's okay so Robbie
それは大丈夫だからロビー
Oh
ああ
but basically the Psalms are have been
基本的に詩篇は
collected and arranged over time and it
収集し、時間をかけて整理し、それ
was the handbook that the Jewish people
ユダヤ人の手紙だった
would use as part of their worship hmm
彼らの礼拝の一部として使用する
and so particularly what we're going to
そして特にそうするつもりです
pick out there's so many good ones and
たくさんの良いものがあることを選んでください。
there's so many songs that we sing that
私たちが歌う歌がたくさんあります
come from the Psalms and so we thought
詩篇から来て、私たちは考えました
that we would just pick out a few that
それをいくつか選んで
have been personally meaningful to us
私たちに個人的に意味があった
and what we're going to do we're just
私たちは何をやろうとしているのですか？
going to read through them and we want
それら を読んで行くと私たちが欲しい
you the viewer either to close your eyes
あなたの 目 を閉じて
or to read along on the screen and one
画面に沿って読むことができます。
of those words that sort of jump out to
ソートの に 飛び出すそれらの言葉の
you and that's um it was very
あなたとそれはまあまあです
interesting I had a conversation with a
面白かったです。
young man who's interested in becoming
なることに興味を持っている若い男
an Anglican priest and he was talking to
聖公会の司祭と彼は話していた
me about why they read the way they do
彼らが自分のやり方を読んだ理由
it's all in monotone voice have you ever
それは単調な声ですべてです
noticed that like Catholic and Anglican
カトリックやアングリカンのように
priest read in this monotone voice like
僧侶はこのモノトーンのような声で読んだ
that surface it's on purpose so that the
その表面は目的に沿っているので、
spirit speaks through the words and puts
精神は言葉と言葉を通して話す
the emphasis on the words that need to
必要な言葉の強調
be emphasized rather than the pastor the
牧師よりも強調される
priest picking the words that need to be
司祭は必要な言葉を選ぶ
emphasized so that way it's all said in
強調されているので、
the exact same way every time so then it
それと同時に、まったく同じ方法
leaves it in the hand of the spirit to
精神の手にそれを残し
do the work rather than the pastor
牧師ではなく仕事をする
that's a very interesting way of going
それは非常に興味深い方法です
about it actually I thought so too
それについて実際に私はあまりにも思った
because so often you know I read it the
あなたは私がそれを読んでいることをよく知っているからです
same way every time than a you know I
あなたが知っているよりも毎回同じ方法で私を知っている
you know you'll read it at somebody else
あなたはあなたが他の誰かにそれを読むことを知っている
will read it's like okay because you
それは大丈夫のようです
want to hear the different voice and
異なる声 を聞きたい
what are the words they're focusing on I
彼らが私に焦点を当てている言葉は何ですか？
think there's something tremendously
途方もない何かがあると思う
powerful listening to the Word of God
神の言葉を力強く聞く
like reading it is one way of taking it
読書のようにそれを取るの一つの方法です
in but there's something so different
そこには何かとても違うものがあります
about hearing the story about hearing
聴覚に関する話を聞くことについて
the song yes and hearing the words of
はい、その言葉を聞いて歌
Christ who another reader i find it
別の読者がそれを見つけるキリスト
tremendously powerful and sometimes a
驚くほど強力で、時には
lot easier to remember yes yes i agree
たくさんの覚えが簡単ですはいはい 私は同意します
you know what's so wonderful about the
あなたは何がすごく素晴らしいか知っています
bible jen is that there's something for
聖書ジェンのための何かがあるということです
everyone it's a historical book it's a
誰もがそれは歴史的な本だ
romance
ロマンス
it's a drama yes it's a comedy and
それはドラマです。はい、これはコメディです。
there's something for have the people
人々 を持つための何かがあります
who love literature love poetry who love
愛する文学愛の詩
music yes and actually one of the band
音楽はい、実際にバンドの 1つ
members in the band I am they if you
バンドのメンバー私は彼らですもしあなた
want to check them out you can get their
彼ら をチェック して みたい
CD actually if you go to our partners
実際にあなたがパートナーに行くならCD
page and go to Amazon mm-hmm you can
ページを開いてAmazonに行くmm-hmm
find their CD there but I just really
そこに自分のCDを見つけることが、 本当に I
appreciated this guy's story and
この男の物語を高く評価した
basically he had gone through a hard
基本的に彼はハードを経験していた
time in his life and decided he played
彼の人生の時間と彼は演奏を決めた
guitar and decided one day that you know
あなたが知っていることを決めた
what he couldn't deal anymore with his
彼はもはや彼とは対処できなかったこと
life he was in high school and that he
彼は高校に通っていて、
was going to commit suicide oh my yeah
ああ私のええ、自殺するつもりだった
and he was thinking about doing it and
彼はそれをやろうと考えていた。
then a girl he met at school came up to
彼が学校で出会った女の子が来て
him and said oh hey like you play guitar
彼と言ったああ、ちょっとあなたがギターを弾くように
that's kind of cool so do I and so they
それは涼しいので、 私もそうです
started talking and she said well why
話を始め、彼女はよく言った
don't you why don't we get together and
あなたはなぜ一緒に暮らしていないのですか？
play after school tomorrow he said yeah
明日学校の後で遊ぶ彼はええ言った
sure so they went went to school the
彼らは学校に行った
next day and then he brought his guitar
次の日、その後 、彼は彼のギターをもたらしました
and then she didn't show up and so he
彼女は現れなかったので、彼は
locked his guitar in the classroom and
教室で彼のギターをロックし、
he was going to go home and commit
彼は家に帰ってコミットしようとしていた
suicide and this girl came running up to
自殺して、この女の子は走ってきた
him later and said no no don't leave
彼は後で、いいえ、いいえ、言ったままにしないでください
don't leave I'm here and he said oh I
私はここにいるままにしないで、彼はああ言った
left my guitar she said you can use my
私のギターを残して、彼女はあなたが私の
guitar and then she started to share the
ギターを披露して
songs that she sings and it's based on
彼女が歌う歌はそれに基づいている
she says did you know that there's
彼女は、 あなたはそれがあることを知っています
actually song book in the Bible Wow and
聖書の中の実際に歌の本
then that's how she used the Bible to
それが彼女が聖書をどのように使って
start telling him about Christ and then
キリストについて話し始めると
he got saved in God has given him new
彼は神に救われた
life essentially because he was going to
本質的に彼は
take his life yeah I'll amazing well
彼の人生を取るええ、私はうまくいくだろう
it's so cool because this is actually
これは実際には素晴らしい
it's called the serendipity student
それ は、セレンディピティ学生と呼ばれる
bible did you come upon it
聖書あなたはそれに来ましたか？
serendipitously ah yes actually lady in
serendipitouslyああ、はい、実際に女性
my church she was our small group leader
私の教会は彼女が私たちの小グループのリーダーでした
and she took us to a course and so this
彼女は私たちをコースに連れて行きました。
is specifically geared for students so
特に学生のために準備されている
there's all sorts of of helps all the
あらゆる種類の助けがあります
way through it for students to
学生のためにそれを通って
understand the Bible better write those
聖書がそれらをよく書くことを理解する
moments when you read something you're
あなたが何かを読んだときの瞬間
like what does that mean yeah and so
好きなことはどういう意味ですか？
there's little things in it so I love
私は愛するので、そこに小さなものがあります
the beginning of the Psalms yeah it
詩篇の始まりええ
right says the moods of the various
右は、様々な
Psalms embraced the whole range of human
詩篇は人間 の全 範囲を 取り入れた
experience from exuberant praise to
豊かな賞賛からの経験
despair from intense anger and doubt
強烈な怒りと疑いからの絶望
about God's care to hope for a future
未来を願う神様の世話について
based precisely upon God's care they can
正確に神の世話に基づいて
help us express emotions that otherwise
それ以外の感情を表現するのに役立ちます
you might not have words for or feel
あなたは言葉を感じないかもしれません。
right about the Psalms catch the reality
Psalmsについてのリアリティは現実をキャッチする
of our up-and-down relationship with God
私たちの神 との上下関係
but they also move a set of the along
しかし、 彼らは また、
the path of not enough knowing God hmm
十分な神のことを知っていないの道hmm
and that's what the Psalms are about and
それが詩篇のことです
that's I think one of the reasons why we
それは私が私たちが
we picked them was like I said to carry
私たちはそれらを選んだ私が運ぶと言ったようだった
what what are some of the Psalms that
どのような詩篇が何であるか
sort of stand out to you and you know
あなたに目立つように
you immediately said you know certain
あなたはすぐにあなたが
ones and and then I was like yeah those
私はそうだった
ones are cool because they elicit
彼らは魅力的です
something as we've read them we've
私たちが読んだとおりのもの
connected it's where whether or not we
それがどこに接続されているのか
were feeling angry or sad or upset or
怒っている、悲しい、怒っている、または
doubting God because so many of these
これらの多くが神を疑う
David is even saying are you even
デイヴィッドはあなたにさえ言っている
listening to me where are you where are
あなたはどこにいますか？
you or he's like you're gonna smite my
あなたや彼はあなたが私の
enemies and you're like yeah and then I
敵とあなたはええのようで、私は
should have been feeling this I should I
私はこれを感じ ていた はずです
be feeling nice and you're like well if
素敵な気分になり、あなたはうまくいく
David felt this way you know so well
デビッドはあなたがとてもよく知っているこのように感じました
then why don't we start read will read
それでは、 読ん で始めないのはなぜですか？
Psalm 1 and it goes like this this is uh
詩篇1とそれは これの よう に行く これ はああです
NIV 1984 version blessed is the man who
NIV 1984年版は祝福された男です
does not walk in the counsel of the
相談の中で 歩いていない
wicked or stand in the way of sinners or
罪人の道を邪悪にする
sit in the seat of mockers but his
奴ら の 座席に座る
delight is in the law of the Lord and on
喜びは主の律法にあります。
his law he meditates day and night he is
彼の法律は彼が昼と夜を瞑想する
like a tree planted by streams of water
水の流れに植えられた木のように
which yields its fruit in season and
それは季節にその果実を生み出す
whose leaf does not wither whether he
彼の葉は枯れていない
did whatever he does prospers not so the
彼が何をしてもそれほど繁栄しなかった
wicked they are like chaff like the wind
邪悪な彼らは風のような羊のようです
like the wind blows away therefore the
したがって、離れて風が吹くように
wicked will not stand in the judgment
邪悪な者は判決に立たない
nor sinners in the Assembly of the
議会の罪人でもない
righteous for the Lord watches over the
主のために正しい者が
way of the righteous but the way of the
義人の道だが、道の道
wicked will perish hmm so Jen you said
邪悪な人はあなたを殺してしまいます。
immediately that this is one of your
すぐにあなたの
favorites so why is that every time I
お気に入りのように
read this Psalm I
この詩篇Iを読む
get a picture okay of a tree beside a
の横の木が大丈夫な写真を撮る
river and its roots are just drinking so
川とその根はちょうど飲んでいるので
full in that river that nothing is ever
その川に満ちていることは何もない
going to knock it over and it says
それをノックするとそれは言う
wonderful big like below no like just
ちょうどいいよ
this leafy big wonderfully shaped maple
この葉っぱの大きい素晴らしい形のメープル
tree you know with the perfectly round
あなたが完全に丸で知っている木
the thick trunk and those wonderful like
太い幹とそのような素晴らしいもの
roots that are going down and you're
ルーツがダウンしているとあなたは
like the kind of tree that you want to
あなたがしたい木のような
lean up against and you're like yeah
あなたと似ています
this tree isn't going anywhere solid
この木はどこにもいらない
shade it's solid like your whole thing
それはあなたのすべてのもののようにしっかりしている
is solid and and you want and like harry
あなたは欲しい、ハリーのように
said it's solid shade like you're
あなたのような堅実な色合いだと言った
sitting there and you're like yeah and
そこに座って、あなたはえっと
then the fact that you know it says and
あなたがそれを知っているという事実と
who's lee it says which yields is fruit
どんな収量が果物だと言うのか
in season and whose leaf does not wither
葉が枯れることはない
whatever he does prospers like it
彼が何をしてもそれが繁栄する
reminds me that if I delight in the law
私が法律を喜んでくれれば
of the Lord that means the Torah or you
あなたの律法を意味する主の
know the entire Scripture or and for
または聖書全体を知る
David in particular it was the Torah he
特に ダビデは 彼の律法であった
was given the Torah and all kings were
トーラとすべての王が与えられた
we're told write out your own copy of
私たちは、 あなた 自身のコピーを 書き出す 語っています
the Torah get it inside of yourself so
トーラーはあなた自身の中にそれを入れます
that you worship me that you know what
あなたが私に拝んで、あなたが何を知っているか
the Torah says yeah which i think is one
私が思う 、トーラはええと言っている
of the reasons why when i do my
なぜ私がそうするのか
devotions i write out the verse there
私はそこに詩を書きます
was something about reading it and
それを読んで
writing it and then making sure I'm
それを書いて、次に私が確信していることを確認する
writing it correctly hey because then it
それを正しく書いてね
comes it comes in it becomes part of who
それが来ると来るのは誰の一部になる
I am and so David is saying you know his
私はだからダビデはあなたに彼のことを知らせている
delight is in the law of the Lord and on
喜びは主の律法にあります。
his law he meditates day and night he is
彼の法律は彼が昼と夜を瞑想する
like a tree planet like so to be that
そうであるように木の惑星のように
that tree that steadfast tree it comes
それは堅実な木であるその木
from meditating on the Word of God like
のような神の言葉を瞑想することから
if we want to be rock solid we need to
私たちが岩場になりたいなら、
delight in the law we need to meditate
私たちが瞑想する必要のある法律を喜ばす
on it and it also goes on like before
それの上にまた前に行く
that says it does not walk in the
それはそれが歩いていないと言います
counsel of the wicked or stand in the
邪悪な者の助言、あるいは
way of
方法の
sinners so he's saying what the what
罪人たちは何を言っているのですか？
what that man does in verse 2 about what
その人は2節で何をしているのか
he doesn't do yes is also important yes
彼ははいをしませんも重要ですはい
yes so it's like he gets his counsel not
彼は彼の助言を得るないようにはいので、それはです
from wicked people so he's actually
彼は実際に邪悪な人たちから
mindful of who he listens to I think
彼が私の言うことを聞いている人を気にする
sometimes we forget about that who are
時には私 たちが誰であるかを忘れる
we surrounding ourselves with who's on
誰がオンであるかで我々自身を取り巻く
that inner circle I'm reminded about
私の心の中に
what Paul says about not being yoked
ポールがヨークにいないと言ったこと
with unbelievers and we often think well
不信者と私たちはしばしばよく考えます
that's business partners or that's your
それはビジネスパートナーです。それはあなたのものです
husband yeah but we don't those people
私たちはその人たちではありません
who are on the inner circle who pour
内側のサークルにいる人は誰ですか？
into our lives do they know Jesus are
私たちの生活の中には、イエスが
they walking with the Lord and if they
彼らは主と共に歩いています。
aren't walking with the Lord how much do
どのように主と一緒に歩いていない
we allow them to speak into us and I
私たちは 彼らに私たちと私に話す ことができ ます
think that can be hard especially if you
特にあなたが
don't come from a Christian family or
キリスト教の家族や
maybe you're the only christian in your
多分あなたはあなたの唯一のキリスト教徒です
home but i think that's where the beauty
私はそれが美しさの場所だと思う
of the church body comes into play yes
教会の体の再生にはいるはい
and we just had a meeting tonight at
私たちは今夜会いました
church and I was so thankful for the
教会と私はとても感謝してい た
older women who have really encouraged
本当に奨励 している高齢の女性
me over over my life so if you're not
私の人生を超えて
part of a church family i encourage you
教会の家族の一員私はあなたを励ます
to step out find a bible-believing
聖書を信じることを踏み出す
church that preaches the gospel and
福音を説く教会
preaches Jesus according to the Bible
イエスは聖書にしたがって説教する
and get connected there with other
そこに他の人とつながる
people who can really encourage you yeah
本当にあなたを励ますことができる人
mm-hmm and so where it says you know he
あなたは彼が知っていると言います
doesn't walk the things he doesn't do
彼がしないことを歩かない
doesn't walk in the counsel of wicked
邪悪な者の勧告の中を歩いていない
doesn't stand in the way of sinners or
罪人の道に立たない
sit in the seat of mockers but he does
嘲笑の席に座るが、彼はする
delight in the Lord and as a result I
主を喜び、結果として私は
always liked the if-then statements he
いつもif-thenのステートメントが好きだった
have if you do this then this will
あなたがこれをすれば、これは
happen yeah and there are so many of
ええ、そういうことがたくさんある
those things in Scripture excuse me I
聖書の中のそれらのことは私を
think we forget about that if we if we
私たちは忘れると思う ならば、私たちの場合、我々
meditate on the law if we are careful
私たちが慎重であれば法律を黙想する
about who's pouring into our lives and
誰が私たちの生活に注ぎ込まれているか
who are hanging out with then we really
私たちは本当に一緒に遊んでいる
be will be like that tree planted by
その植えられた木のようになります
streams of waters who leaves don't
ない葉の水の流れ
wither who brings forth fruit in season
季節に果実をもたらす枯れた者
whatever he does prospers now that does
彼が何をしても今は繁栄している
not a good deal is a good deal you would
良いことではないでしょうか？
think it is a good deal and you know and
それは良い取引だと思います。
prospers means does well it doesn't mean
繁栄する手段はうまくいくわけではありません
you're making a million dollars every
毎回100万ドルを稼いでいます
day but it means whatever you put your
それはあなたが何を置くかを意味します
hand to ya prosper like Joseph yeah
ヨセフのように繁栄する
there will be blessing in it yeah and
それには恵みがあります
then I love the fact that it goes on to
私はそれが続くことを愛する
say not so the wicked they're like chaff
彼らは邪悪な人ではないと言って
they are like chaff that the wind blows
彼らは風が吹くような籾殻のようです
away and they will not stand in the
離れて、彼らはに立っていないだろう
judgment nor in the righteous in the set
セットでの判断も正義で
Assembly of the righteous like because
のような義人の集合
they are choosing not to follow God they
彼らは神に従わないことを選んでいる
will not receive heaven and it's very
天国を受け取ることはないでしょう。
clear like the righteous to be righteous
正義のように義人のようにはっきりと
means to be right with God it doesn't
そうでない神と右にあることを意味します
mean that you you know you do all the
あなたはあなたがすべての
right things because lots of people
たくさんの人々のために正しいこと
think that they're good and there are
彼らは良いと思うし、そこにいる
lots of good people but they're not
良い人がたくさんいますが、そうではありません
right with God and that is the only way
神と一緒にいて、それが唯一の方法です
to heaven is to be right with God in the
天国への道は神と共に
only way that we can ever be right with
私たちがこれまでに正しいことができる唯一の方法
God is through the work that Jesus did
神はイエスがなされた仕事を通じて
on the cross I think as believers
十字架上で私は信者として考える
sometimes we can get caught up in the
時には私たちは
good things that we do and we are called
私たちがして、 私たちは呼ばれている良いもの
to do good things but that's not all
良いことをするが、それ は すべてで はない
were saved by yeah and you know I got to
救われたと私は知っている
admit that recently you know I've been
最近私が知っていることを認めている
really busy doing things doing lots of
本当に忙しい
things you know helping whatever but I
あなたが知っているものは何でも助けてくれます
was neglecting spending as much time in
多くの時間を費やしていた
the Word of God yeah and when I look at
神の言葉ええと私が見るとき
what it says but his delight is in the
それは言いますが、彼の喜びは
law of the Lord and in his law he
主の律法と彼の法則
meditates day and night I realized that
昼と夜を瞑想する
a lot of what i was listening to was not
私が聞い ていた ことの多く はそうではありませんでした。
actually the word I never listened to a
実際に私が聞い た ことのない言葉
lot of music I listen to a lot of
私はたくさんの音楽を聞いています
podcasts sometimes teaching about like
ポッドキャスティングは時には同じように教える
philosophy and medicine and all that
哲学と医学とそのすべて
stuff which is good but it's not the
良いものですが、それはない
Word of God which is transformative yes
変容的である神の言葉
and so I decided for a week to not
それで私は1週間はないと決めました
listen to those things and to only
それらのことを聞いて
listen to an audio Bible hmm and I
オーディオ聖書に耳を傾け、私は
thought maybe I wasn't taking in a lot
おそらく私は多くを取っていないと思った
of it but I noticed that my disposition
それの私の気質が気づいた
has changed the way I my first thoughts
私の最初の考え方を変えた
are not the same they're more geared
同じではありませんよりギアードされている
towards thinking about
思考に向かって
God or to pray about someone else yeah
神か他の誰かについて祈るために
so you know that's an easy way to be
あなたはそれが簡単な方法であることを知っています
meditating on the Word of God is just
神の言葉を瞑想するだけです
kind of replacing something else you're
他の何かを置き換えるもの
listening to with with the word kind of
単語の種類で聞いて
so cool yeah but that's that's an
だからクールなええ、それはそれです
example of how you can get the Word of
あなたがどのようにあなたの言葉を得ることができるかの例
God in is by fasting from something like
神様のようなものから断食することです
fasting from you know watching a half
あなたからの断食は、半分を見て知っている
hour of TV or netflix and say you know
テレビやネットフリックスの時間とあなたが知っていると言う
what I'm going to take that half an hour
私はそれを30分かかります
and I'm going to spend it with the Lord
私は主と一緒に過ごすつもりです
it because so often people are likely I
それほど頻繁に人々は私がそうである可能性が高いので
don't have time to read my Bible and we
私の聖書 を読む時間がありません。
want to encourage you as we're beginning
私たちが始めている間にあなたを励ましたい
this new year or whenever you happen to
この新年、またはいつでもあなたに起こる
listen you know it's always a new start
いつでも新しいスタートだと分かっています
then just make a new start don't say
それからちょうど新しいスタートを言わないで
well I'll just wait till next week or
まあ、私は来週まで待つか、
I'll wait till neck make the new starts
私は首が新しいスタートを作るまで待つだろう
a day his mercy is new every day and
彼の慈悲は毎日新しいものです。
verse 6 says for the Lord watches over
6節は、主が守るために
the way of the righteous but the way of
正義の道、しかし道の道
the wicked will perish like don't put it
邪悪な者はそれを置かないように滅びるでしょう
off don't put it off if you're feeling
あなたが感じているならばそれを外してはいけません
convicted now like okay I need and then
私が必要とする大丈夫のように今や有罪判決を受けた
just push pause on the video right now
今すぐビデオを一時停止してください
oh and go open it up and just go open it
ああ、それを開いて、それを開いて行く
up turn to someone and let God speak to
誰かに回って神が話すようにしなさい
you yeah but it's interesting every time
あなたはええ、それは毎回面白いです
and I love the fact that this is at the
そして私はこれが である という事実を愛します
very beginning of the Psalms because it
それは詩篇の始まりです。
draws me in I want to read more because
私はので多くを読みたいで私を描きます
I want to be right before God but i also
私は神の前にいたいが、 私 もまた
want to produce fruit but that comes
果物を生産したいが、それが来る
from that relationship with god it's
神との関係から
like I love Jesus and because I love
私がイエスを愛しているように
Jesus then I want to do I want to do the
イエスは、私は私が やりたい やりたいです
right things i do want to produce fruit
私は 果物を作り たい と 思う正しいもの
but then that comes from wheat reading
しかしそれは小麦の読書に由来する
his word which causes me to love him
私に彼を愛させる彼の言葉
even more which it's this cycle that we
さらにこれがこのサイクルです
need to get in and it starts by reading
入る必要があり、それは読書によって始まります
the word and that comes you want to bear
言葉とそれはあなたが耐えたいと思って来る
fruits of righteousness and the New
正義の成果と新
Testament talks about the fruit of
証言の果実についての証言
righteousness right and we're righteous
正義と私たちは正義です
by faith in Christ so we can't actually
キリストの信仰によって、私たちは実際には
bear fruit that's right just unless we
私たちが
are first in Christ realizing what he's
彼が何をしているのかを最初に理解している
done for us yeah and then reading his
私たちのためにやったし、彼を読んで
word yeah right so as we finish off this
私たちがこれを終わらせるように言葉ええそうです
episode there's a couple things we want
エピソードには、私たちが望むカップルのものがあります
you to think about specifically who is
具体的に誰が考えているか
pouring into your life who is in your
であるあなたの人生に注いあなた
inner inner circle who are you listening
あなたが聞いている内側の内側のサークル
to are you allowing
あなたは許可していますか？
people who don't know Jesus to be the
イエス・キリストを知らない人
main the lattice wise they need to be in
彼らが必要とする格子をメインにする
your life no we're not saying not to
あなたの 人生私たちが言っているわけではない
have them in your life but what we are
あなたの人生でそれらを持っているが、私たち は 何か
saying is who's the loudest voice so
誰が一番大きな声だと言っている
making sure that you take stock of who
あなたが誰の株式を取っていることを確認する
actually speaking into your into your
実際にあなたのことを話す
life and secondly are you delighting in
第二にあなたは喜んでいる
the law of the lord are you spending
主の法律はあなたが費やしている
time in his word so that actually that
実際にその ように彼の言葉の時間
becomes most loudest voice at all of all
すべての中で最も大きな声になる
so that when people say things or stuff
人々が物事や物を言うときに
happens then you go to the word you're
あなたはあなたの言葉に行く
like okay well this is what the Bible
大丈夫のようにこれは聖書のことです
says yeah so we encourage you to do to
ええ、私たちはあなたにすることをお勧めします
do those two things to take stock of
の株式を取るために、これらの2つのことを行います
who's the loudest voice and secondly are
誰が一番大きな声で、二番目に
you meditating on the on the Word of God
あなたは神 の 言葉について瞑想する
and then are you producing fruit are you
あなたは果物を産んでいますか？
producing righteous fruit as Kerry says
ケリーが言うように正義のフルーツを生産する
and I realize that it's always in cycles
私はそれが常にサイクルであることを認識します
and some days we produce way more fruit
いくつかの日、私たちはもっと多くの果物を作ります
and sometimes it feels like it's a
時にはそれが
drought but the Lord has a seasons right
干ばつだが、主は季節の権利を持っている
it's there are seasons to fruit
それは果実に季節がある
production and so we encourage you to
私たちはあなたに
spend some time with Lord reading over
主が読んでいる時間を過ごす
some one and and ask him to speak to you
ある人とあなたに話すように彼に尋ねる
about those three things all right well
大丈夫な3つのことについて
why don't we just pray all right thank
なぜ私たちはすべての権利を祈るだけでは ありがとう
you Father for your word mm-hmm I pray
あなたの言葉のためにお父さんmm-hmm私は祈ります
that you'd write it on our heart and
あなたはそれを私たちの心に書いて
mind it has us to delight in it and that
それはそれで楽しませてくれてい て 、 その 気に
you use your were your truth together I
あなたはあなたの真実を一緒に使っています。
pray that you would help us and our
あなたと私たちを助けることを祈ってください
viewers to hunger and thirst for
飢えと渇きの視聴者
righteousness and to be reading your
正義を読んで
word regularly thank you so much thank
定期的に感謝してくれてありがとう
you so much for them thank you so much
あなたにはとても感謝しています
for Jen and Robbie and just the whole
JenとRobbieのために、ちょうど全体
team that makes this happen it's in
それが起こるようにするチーム
Jesus name we pray amen amen well we
イエスの名、私たちはよくアーメンアーメン私たちを祈ります
look forward to seeing you next
次回にお会いできることを楽しみにしています
same time same website new everyday TV
同じ時間に同じウェブサイト新しい毎日のテレビ
and I'll put your tune in for another
そして、 私は 別のものにあなたの曲を 出してあげます
self I feel a song coming on right on
自己私は右に来る曲を感じる
next week
来週
you
君は